Paul Baran Papers M1817
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Paul Baran papers
1952-2004
M1817
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
255.0 Linear feet
Included are papers from Baran's time at RAND, Institute for the Future, CableData Associates, Comprint, Equatorial Communications, Telebit, Packet Technologies, Stratacom, Metricom, Interfax, Com21, Rosum, as well as numerous public service committees and non-profit organizations.
Access to Collection
The materials are open for research use. Audio-visual materials are not available in original format, and must be reformatted to a digital use copy.
Acquisition Information
Gift of The Paul and Evelyn Baran Trust, 2011. Accession 2011-051.
Scope and Contents
Included are papers from Baran's time at RAND, Institute for the Future, CableData Associates, Comprint, Equatorial Communications, Telebit, Packet Technologies, Stratacom, Metricom, Interfax, Com21, Rosum, as well as numerous public service committees and non-profit organizations.
Biographical Note
Paul Baran, 1926-2011, was a Polish-American engineer who helped create the technical underpinnings for the Arpanet, the government-sponsored precursor to today's Internet. He was one of the three earliest researchers of packet switching techniques, and went on to start several companies and develop other technologies that are an essential part of the Internet and other modern digital communication.
- RAND Date:980001 (Container 1, Folder 1)
  Annual Report, 1998
- RAND Date:980408 (Container 1, Folder 2)
  Address Commemorating RAND'S 50th Anniversary (James Wilson)
- RAND Date:980721 (Container 1, Folder 3)
  Invitation for Boris Berezovsky, Sec. General of Commonwealth of Independent States
- RAND Date:980919 (Container 1, Folder 4)
  RAND Alumni Study Group - Organizational Meeting
- RAND Date:980924 (Container 1, Folder 5)
  Meeting to Discuss Science and Technology Related Activities
- RAND Date:980926 (Container 1, Folder 6)
  Day at RAND: "Financial Crises & Contagion in Emerging Markets: Why Asia, Why Now?"
- RAND Date:981001 (Container 1, Folder 7)
  RAND Alumni Bulletin, Winter 1998
- RAND Date:981001 (Container 1, Folder 8)
  RAND Review: 50 Years of Looking Forward, Special Comemorative Issue
- RAND Date:981115 (Container 1, Folder 9)
  The Seven Day Week (memo from Blumenthal)
- RAND Date:981130 (Container 1, Folder 10)
  Invitation to join Board of Governors (from Klitgaard)
- RAND Date:981201 (Container 1, Folder 11)
  RAND Outreach to Bay Area and Silicon Valley
- RAND Date:981221 (Container 1, Folder 12)
  Background on Dick Leghorn (from Osterholt)
- RAND Date:990001 (Container 1, Folder 13)
  2 Catalogs: International Policy, Military Affairs and Social Sciences
- RAND Date:990116 (Container 1, Folder 14)
  Town Hall Forum on Criminal Justice Policy
- RAND Date:990304 (Container 1, Folder 15)
  Biographical Sketches of Those Admitted for 1999 (& request for candidates for Bd. Of Gov.)
- RAND Date:990331 (Container 1, Folder 16)
  Invitation List for May 12, briefing by Steve Carroll on Higher Education
- RAND Date:990030 (Container 1, Folder 17)
  RAND Review: Common Interests, Common Responsibilities, Spring 1999
- RAND Date:990401 (Container 1, Folder 18)
  RAND Alumni Bulletin, Spring 1999
- RAND Date:990407 (Container 1, Folder 19)
  President's Council Meeting, Washington
- RAND Date:990430 (Container 1, Folder 20)
  RAND/AirTouch Policy Forum
- RAND Date:000611 (Container 1, Folder 21)
  Policy Forum: "Terrorism and Counterterrorism" Reflections on Recent Events & Developments"
- RAND Date:990621 (Container 1, Folder 22)
  Delay of proposal "Economic Potential of Upcoming Open Skies Reconnaissance Satellites"
- RAND Date:990702 (Container 1, Folder 23)
  Newsreleases and Clippings
- RAND Date:990715 (Container 1, Folder 24)
  New Paradigms and Parallels" the Printing Press and the Internet"
- RAND Date:991008 (Container 1, Folder 25)
  CyberAssurance: Meeting Challenges to Information-age Security
- RAND Date:991026 (Container 1, Folder 26)
  RAND'S Santa Monica Property
- RAND Date:991129 (Container 1, Folder 27)
  Forbes, "The Rich Were Different"
- RAND Date:990525 (Container 1, Folder 28)
  Economic Potential of upcoming "Open Skies" Reconnaissance Satellites
- RAND Date:990803 (Container 1, Folder 29)
  A Workshop on Parallels between the Printing Press and the Internet
- RAND Date:991108 (Container 1, Folder 30)
- RAND Date:991110 (Container 1, Folder 31)
  President's Council Meeting, Santa Monica
- RAND Date:991130 (Container 1, Folder 32)
  Security in Cyberspace
- RAND Date:000101 (Container 1, Folder 33)
  A Center for the Analysis of Advancing Information Technologies (Planning Grant Proposal)
- RAND Date:000110 (Container 1, Folder 34)
  Update on the New RSMD/HR Office, and 3 RAND Items
- RAND Date:000209 (Container 1, Folder 35)
  Leadership Change in NSRD, plus 2 Rand Items
- RAND Date:000630 (Container 1, Folder 36)
  The Printing Press and the Internet, sponsored by Bertelsmann Fdn, RAND, Nanyang Tech. Univ.
- RAND Date:000312 (Container 1, Folder 37)
  Email from Jim Dewar regarding PB attending Bertelsmann Fdn. Sponsored conference
- RAND Date:001023 (Container 1, Folder 38)
  Outreach Reception Information (Lists,Briefing Info, Invitation, etc)
- RAND Date:650830 (Container 2, Folder 1)
  Recommendation to Air Staff: "Development of the Distributed Adaptive Message-Block Network"
- RAND Date:730301 (Container 2, Folder 2)
  RAND Consulting "Outline of Major ARPA Sub Net Experiment" and others
- RAND Date:920309 (Container 2, Folder 3)
  The Information Society: An International Journal (R. Anderson)
- RAND Date:930527 (Container 2, Folder 4)
  Panel Discussion on "Effects of the Information Revolution on Society"
- RAND Date:940001 (Container 2, Folder 5)
  Annual Report
- RAND Date:940509 (Container 2, Folder 6)
  The Feasibility and Social implications of universal Email Access in the U.S.
- RAND Date:940701 (Container 2, Folder 7)
  Center for Information Revolution Alalysis (CIRA)
- RAND Date:960622 (Container 2, Folder 8)
  50th Project Air Force
- RAND Date:960821 (Container 2, Folder 9)
  Alumni Reception in Bay Area (hosted by PB)
- RAND Date:961001 (Container 2, Folder 10)
  RAND Alumni Bulletins
- RAND Date:970601 (Container 2, Folder 11)
  Various Newsletters
- RAND Date:970601 (Container 2, Folder 12)
  Graduate School Bulletin, 1997-1999
- RAND Date:970813 (Container 2, Folder 13)
  News Releases: States Alone Unlikely to Solve Problem of Health Care Uninsured, Tobacco Litigants, etc.
- RAND Date:970820 (Container 2, Folder 14)
  Altcom Background Discussion
- RAND Date:970909 (Container 2, Folder 15)
  News Releases
- RAND Date:971001 (Container 2, Folder 16)
  RAND Alumni Bulletin, Winter
- RAND Date:971126 (Container 2, Folder 17)
  National Security Stories
- RAND Date:971210 (Container 2, Folder 18)
  Digital Evolution
- RAND Date:971217 (Container 2, Folder 19)
  PB's Funding Idea - RAND and Digital Evolution
- RAND Date:971223 (Container 2, Folder 20)
  The Fabulous RAND Years in the Computer Science Department
- RAND Date:980001 (Container 2, Folder 21)
  The RAND Corporation, 1988-1989
- RAND Date:980114 (Container 2, Folder 22)
  Misc. (memo to President's Council, Boor Order, Haskins Lecture Series)
- RAND Date:980211 (Container 2, Folder 23)
  Wohlstetter work on RAND web page
- RAND Date:980216 (Container 2, Folder 24)
  Jim Thompson re: Younger Trustee Nominations
- RAND Date:980324 (Container 2, Folder 25)
  A Day at RAND
- RAND Date:980408 (Container 2, Folder 26)
  President's Council Meeting - 50th Anniversary
- RAND Date:980423 (Container 2, Folder 27)
  Jim Thompson Meeting
- RAND Date:980501 (Container 2, Folder 28)
  Willis Ware Reprint (Cyber-Posture of the National Inform. Infrastructure
- RAND Date:980505 (Container 2, Folder 29)
  Confirmation of RAND reservations for 50th Anniversary GALA
- RAND Date:980601 (Container 2, Folder 30)
  Next President's Council Meetings (Nov. 10 and April 12)
- RAND Date:980618 (Container 2, Folder 31)
  Policy Forum: The Insiders' View of National Security Policymaking
- RAND Date:980711 (Container 2, Folder 32)
  Graduate School Commencement Invitation
- RAND Date:980721 (Container 2, Folder 33)
  News Reprints
- RAND Date:980819 (Container 2, Folder 34)
  Land Development Project in Santa Monica
- RAND Date:980901 (Container 2, Folder 35)
  RAND Review - Special Commemorative Issue
- RAND Date:980917 (Container 2, Folder 36)
  Coruption: Beyond Shame, Apathy, Futility by Robert Klitgaard
- RAND Date:981009 (Container 2, Folder 37)
  President's Council Meeting
- RAND Date:981026 (Container 2, Folder 38)
  Policy Forum: Political Violence in the Northern persian Gulf (Jerrold Green)
- RAND Date:981104 (Container 2, Folder 39)
  Graduate School Entering Class 1998-99
- RAND Date:981203 (Container 2, Folder 40)
  Meeting with Jim Osterholt and Barry Balmat
- RAND Date:981217 (Container 2, Folder 41)
  Invitation to attend panel on "What Are the Next Strategies for K - 12 Education Reform"
- CableData Date:741018 (Container 3, Folder 1)
  S-161: "A 6-item Menu of Work for ARPA/IPTO of Particular Interest to Cable Data Asso."
- CableData Date:741116 (Container 3, Folder 2)
  B-164: "Briefing on Economics of Procurement Automation"
- CableData Date:741218 (Container 3, Folder 3)
  Preliminary Agenda - Meeting at CableData Asso. with Meyer and McCloud, Brunswick
- CableData Date:741219 (Container 3, Folder 4)
  S-166: "GAMECOM - A Broad Spectrum Computer Based Game Medium"
- CableData Date:750101 (Container 3, Folder 5)
  Cost Analysis: Development of Gamecom, 1-Year target Program
- CableData Date:750101 (Container 3, Folder 6)
  P-175: "CableData Associates -- A Brief Description"
- CableData Date:750106 (Container 3, Folder 7)
  S-169: "A New High Technology Home Alarm & Communication System"
- CableData Date:750106 (Container 3, Folder 8)
- CableData Date:750109 (Container 3, Folder 9)
  R-170: New Applications, Vol. 1, "On the Automation of the Procurement Process"
- CableData Date:750109 (Container 3, Folder 10)
  R-171: "New Applications, Vol. 2, "Security in the Auto. Procurement Process, Security vs. Efficiency"
- CableData Date:750113 (Container 3, Folder 11)
  Applied Research on Public Regulation & Economic Productivity
- CableData Date:750117 (Container 3, Folder 12)
  S-172: "Proposal to Conduct Research on the Eco. Issues in Intelligent Terminal Research & Applications"
- CableData Date:750120 (Container 3, Folder 13)
  S-173: "Unsolicited Proposal to Conduct Applied Research in Tech. Transfer of Large Computer-Comm,"etc
- CableData Date:750204 (Container 3, Folder 14)
  P-174: Remarks on Larsson's "Allocation of Resources of Computers & Telecommunications"
- CableData Date:750201 (Container 3, Folder 15)
  A Proposition Presented at a recent OECD Conference on Computer/Telecommunication Policy
- CableData Date:750407 (Container 3, Folder 16)
  S-178-1: "Business Plan -- Termcom Model 201"
- CableData Date:750418 (Container 3, Folder 17)
  S-179: "Abstract: Alarmcom Venture"
- CableData Date:750502 (Container 3, Folder 18)
  S-181: "AMC Word Processing Technology & Application Study"
- CableData Date:750605 (Container 3, Folder 19)
  S-183: "Farsi Computer/Telecommunications Terminal Development Program: Two Options"
- CableData Date:790429 (Container 3, Folder 20)
  S-180: "A New High Technology Home Alarm & Communication System", Alarmcom - Model 100
- CableData Date:761201 (Container 3, Folder 1)
  P-221: "Some Perspectives on Networks: Past, Present and Future"
- CableData Date:761230 (Container 3, Folder 2)
  M-248: "CableData Program Status, Progress Report #1"
- CableData Date:770304 (Container 3, Folder 3)
  M-249: " CableData, Progress Report #2"
- CableData Date:770405 (Container 3, Folder 4)
  M-251: "CableData, Progress Report #4"
- CableData Date:770414 (Container 3, Folder 5)
  M-234: "A Proposed Tax Shelter Limited Partnership"
- CableData Date:770415 (Container 3, Folder 6)
  N-250: "CableData, Progress Report #3"
- CableData Date:770510 (Container 3, Folder 7)
  S-240-1: "Low Cost Satellite Electronic Message Services for Rural Areas of the World"
- CableData Date:770601 (Container 3, Folder 8)
  S-239: "An Automated Cassette Tape Library System"
- CableData Date:770705 (Container 3, Folder 9)
  M-252: "Progress Report #4"
- CableData Date:770715 (Container 3, Folder 10)
  Venture Capital Discussions
- CableData Date:771117 (Container 3, Folder 11)
  M-255: "Preliminary Working Paper #1, McGraw-Hill Dodge Reports Distribution"
- CableData Date:771130 (Container 3, Folder 12)
  M- 257: "Progress Report #5"
- CableData Date:741218 (Container 5, Folder 1)
  167: Preliminary Agenda, meeting at CableData Dec. 18, 1974, with Brunswick
- CableData Date:741219 (Container 5, Folder 2)
- CableData Date:741201 (Container 5, Folder 3)
  note, begins on page 16 (no title)
- CableData Date:750101 (Container 5, Folder 4)
  P-175:"CableData Associates -- A Brief Description"
- CableData Date:750106 (Container 5, Folder 5)
  S-169: "A New High Technology Home Alarm and Communication System"
- CableData Date:750101 (Container 5, Folder 6)
  168: "Cost Analysis - Development of Gamecom, 1-Year Target Program"
- CableData Date:750117 (Container 5, Folder 7)
  S-172: "Proposal to Conduct Research on Economic Issues in Intelligent Terminal Research & Applications"
- CableData Date:750120 (Container 5, Folder 8)
  S-173: "Unsolicited Proposal to Conduct Applied Research in Technology Transfer..."
- CableData Date:750203 (Container 5, Folder 9)
  R-165: "New Applications for Arpanet Developed Information Processing Tech, VIII
- CableData Date:750206 (Container 5, Folder 10)
  P-174: "Remarks on Mr. Larsson's Paper, 'Allocation of Resources of Computers & Telecommunications'."
- CableData Date:750214 (Container 5, Folder 11)
  Comments on OECD Conference re: most OECD countries are in stage of transition from industrial to post-industrial economy
- CableData Date:750401 (Container 5, Folder 12)
  S-179: "Abstract - Alarmcom Venture"
- CableData Date:750407 (Container 5, Folder 13)
- CableData Date:750429 (Container 5, Folder 14)
  S-180: "Alarmcom - Model 100, A New High Technology Home Alarm & Communication System"
- CableData Date:750502 (Container 5, Folder 15)
  S-181: "AMC Word Processing Technology and Application Study"
- CableData Date:750529 (Container 5, Folder 16)
  S-176: "Innovations in Degree and Type of Regulation"
- CableData Date:750605 (Container 5, Folder 17)
  S-183: "Farsi Computer/Telecommunications Terminal Development Program - Two Options"
- CableData Date:750701 (Container 5, Folder 18)
  S-186: "Is Electronic Mail Technically and Economically Feasible Today?" (Baran)
- CableData Date:750708 (Container 5, Folder 19)
  S-184-1-A: "Termcom Business Plan, Volume I"
- CableData Date:750714 (Container 5, Folder 20)
  S-187: Termcom (Iran),"A Proposed Joint Iranian/U.S. Computer & Telecommunications Terminal Company"
- CableData Date:750716 (Container 5, Folder 21)
  S-188: "Gamecom Business Plan"
- CableData Date:751101 (Container 5, Folder 22)
  S-182: "On the Definition of the Information sector of the Economy, and its policy Implications"
- CableData Date:750203 (Container 5, Folder 23)
  R-171: "New Applications for Arpanet Developed Information Processing Technology"
- CableData Date:750203 (Container 5, Folder 24)
  R-170: "New Applications for Arpanet Developed Information Processing Technology - Volume 1
- CableData Date:770801 (Container 5, Folder 25)
  P-185-4: "Brief Description of CableData Associates"
- Cabledata Date:750317 (Container 6, Folder 1)
  Federal Register, "Computer Data Protection"; Computer Terminal Network Privacy/Secrecy System
- Cabledata Date:760330 (Container 6, Folder 2)
  Flipping Transformations: A Method of Compressing Large Font Very High Resolution Characters into Small Read Only Memories
- Cabledata Date:800703 (Container 6, Folder 3)
  Notes on Cryptocheck Discussion
- Cabledata Date:811001 (Container 6, Folder 4)
  Document Number Log for Working Papers and Reports
- Cabledata Date:820101 (Container 6, Folder 5)
  Dynapac DP-1000; DCX825, Statistical Multiplexer
- Cabledata Date:820204 (Container 6, Folder 6)
  Letter to Mathews from Brewer (letter opened in error)
- Cabledata Date:820320 (Container 6, Folder 7)
  Filing System Description
- Cabledata Date:820705 (Container 6, Folder 8)
  Business Week, "Satellite Costs that are Down to Earth"
- Cabledata Date:820827 (Container 6, Folder 9)
  Various letters (Brewer, Pospisil, Lubarsky, record of meeting with TTI on Oct. 26, 1981)
- Cabledata Date:831020 (Container 6, Folder 10)
  Data Communications, "Modem Price, Design Bring Data to Analog PBXs"; Report on Telebit (Hanes)
- Cabledata Date:840127 (Container 6, Folder 11)
  Unanimous Written Consent of Shareholders of Packetcable (stock plan)
- Cabledata Date:851021 (Container 6, Folder 12)
  Satellite Comunications System & Apparatus - Reissue of U.S. Patent 4,455,651; paper of May 28, 1979
- (Container 7)
  PB Papers 1970-1971 box 1
- (Container 8)
  PB papers 1970-1971 box 2
- (Container 9)
  PB papers 1970-1971 box 3
- CableData Date:680801 (Container 12, Folder 1)
  RM-5708-RC: "Binary Coded Gun Barrels to Discourage illegal use of Small Arms" (Baran)
- CableData Date:761230 (Container 12, Folder 2)
  M-248: Program Status
- CableData Date:770301 (Container 12, Folder 3)
  S-223: Termcom Presentation
- CableData Date:770304 (Container 12, Folder 4)
  M-249: Progress Report
- CableData Date:770304 (Container 12, Folder 5)
  M-224: Termcom Proprietary Information Agreement
- CableData Date:770309 (Container 12, Folder 6)
  S-226: "Development of a Very Low Cost Satellite Electronic Message Service for Rural Areas"
- CableData Date:770401 (Container 12, Folder 7)
  S-225: "Options for Energy Savings in Residences using Microcomputer Controls"
- CableData Date:770401 (Container 12, Folder 8)
  S-227: "Research Toward Discouragement of Illegal Use of Rifles and Handguns"
- CableData Date:770414 (Container 12, Folder 9)
  M-234: "Cabledate Partners; A Proposed Tax Shelter Limited Partnership"
- CableData Date:770415 (Container 12, Folder 10)
  M-250: Progress Report #3
- CableData Date:770421 (Container 12, Folder 11)
  M:235: "SRI/Savin Review of Plain Paper Printing"
- CableData Date:770427 (Container 12, Folder 12)
  S-233-1: Termcom Business Plan, Section 6, Financial Plan
- CableData Date:770427 (Container 12, Folder 13)
  S-230-1: Termcom Business Plan, Section 3, Marketing Plan
- CableData Date:770427 (Container 12, Folder 14)
  S-231-1: Termcom Business Plan, Section 4, Manufacturing Plan
- CableData Date:770428 (Container 12, Folder 15)
  S-237: "Research to Improve Home Electrical Safely and Reduce Energy Costs"
- CableData Date:770428 (Container 12, Folder 16)
  M-238: "Revised Business Plan" (note - plan not attached)
- CableData Date:770601 (Container 12, Folder 17)
- CableData Date:770615 (Container 12, Folder 18)
  S-241: "Development and Application of Satellite Ground Stations for Use in Electronic Message, etc."
- CableData Date:770623 (Container 12, Folder 20)
  S-242: "Design and Construction of a Satellite Ground Station for Transportable Communications etc"
- CableData Date:770623 (Container 12, Folder 21)
  S-242: "Design and Construction of a Satellite Ground Station for Transportable Communications
- CableData Date:770705 (Container 12, Folder 22)
  M-251: Progress Report #4
- CableData Date:770708 (Container 12, Folder 23)
  S-243: Termcom Business Plan Addendum #1 (to plan of April 27, 1977)
- CableData Date:770715 (Container 12, Folder 24)
  M-252: Associates Meeting July 15, 1977
- CableData Date:770726 (Container 12, Folder 25)
  S-229-1: Termcom Business Plan, Section 2, Product Line and Product Planning
- CableData Date:770728 (Container 12, Folder 26)
  S-228-2: Termcom Business Plan, Section 1, Summary
- CableData Date:770728 (Container 12, Folder 27)
  Termcom Business Plan, Table of Contents
- CableData Date:770728 (Container 12, Folder 28)
  S-232-2: Termcom Business Plan, Section 5, Management & Staffing Plan
- CableData Date:770801 (Container 12, Folder 29)
  M-246: Comments on Termcom Single investor Financing Proposal
- CableData Date:770804 (Container 12, Folder 30)
  S-244: Addendum#1 to "An Automated Cassette Tape Library System (S-239)"
- CableData Date:770817 (Container 12, Folder 31)
  S-247: Review of Electronic Message Services - Proposal Submitted to the Federal Communications, etc.
- CableData Date:770912 (Container 12, Folder 32)
  Don Rogers - Debriefing (with Myers)
- CableData Date:771026 (Container 12, Folder 33)
  S-240-2: "Low Cost Satellite Electronic Message Services for Rural Areas of the World" (revised from May 10)
- CableData Date:771102 (Container 12, Folder 34)
  S-253: Operating Plan
- CableData Date:771108 (Container 12, Folder 35)
  S-236-1: "Research in Improving Telecommunications for the Deaf"
- CableData Date:771114 (Container 12, Folder 36)
  M-254: Mylar Requirements
- CableData Date:771117 (Container 12, Folder 37)
  M-255: Preliminary Working Paper #1; McGraw-Hill Dodge Reports Distribution (Baran)
- CableData Date:771130 (Container 12, Folder 38)
  M-257: Progress Report #5
- CableData Date:771201 (Container 12, Folder 39)
  M-256: Specifications - Table 2-1, Model 201RH Tentative Specifications
- CableData Date:771201 (Container 12, Folder 40)
  M-261: NSF Concept Paper - Technological Aids for Improving the Productivity of Physically Handicapped
- CableData Date:771201 (Container 12, Folder 41)
  M-259 (note - no information)
- CableData Date:771213 (Container 12, Folder 42)
  M-258: "Line-at-a-Time Printer Product Order Specification, Planning Aid"
- CableData Date:780101 (Container 12, Folder 43)
  P-260: "The Future of Packet Switching"
- CableData Date:780314 (Container 12, Folder 44)
  M-263: Muzak Modulation (Warner)
- CableData Date:780328 (Container 12, Folder 45)
  M-264: Progress Report #6
- CableData Date:780401 (Container 12, Folder 46)
  S-262: Stage 1 - Business Plan
- CableData Date:730727 (Container 13, Folder 1)
  CAWP-101: "The Proposed Arpanet Divestiture: Legal Questions and Economic Issues", Goldstein
- CableData Date:730810 (Container 13, Folder 2)
  CAWP-#103: "Key Individuals Concerned with Packet-Switching Standards in the U. S.," Crane
- CableData Date:730810 (Container 13, Folder 3)
- CableData Date:731015 (Container 13, Folder 4)
  R-105: "The Applicability of Microcomputer Based Technology to a Mobile, High-Altitude, etc.
- CableData Date:740418 (Container 13, Folder 5)
  S-146: "Review of Microform Storage & Retrieval Systems Suitable for Computer Controlled Retrieval"
- CableData Date:741018 (Container 13, Folder 6)
  S-161: "A Six-item Menu of Work for ARPA/IPTO of Particular Interest to CableData Associates"
- CableData Date:750106 (Container 13, Folder 7)
- CableData Date:750109 (Container 13, Folder 8)
- CableData Date:750117 (Container 13, Folder 9)
  S-172: "Proposal to Conduct Research on Economic Issues in Intelligent Terminal Research & Applications," Cerf
- CableData Date:750203 (Container 13, Folder 10)
  R-170: New Applications for Arpanet Developed Information Processing Technology, Agnew,Baran,etc, Vol 1
- CableData Date:750203 (Container 13, Folder 11)
  R-170: "New Applications for Arpanet Developed Information Processing Technology" Agnew,Baran,etc, Vol 1
- CableData Date:750203 (Container 13, Folder 12)
  R-171: New Applications for Arpanet Developed Information Processing Technology, Vol 11
- CableData Date:750407 (Container 13, Folder 13)
- CableData Date:750620 (Container 13, Folder 14)
  S-184-2: "Appendices to Termcom Business Plan, V11"
- CableData Date:750708 (Container 13, Folder 15)
  S-184-1-A: "Termcom Business Plan, V1"
- CableData Date:750820 (Container 13, Folder 16)